it's completing it says there's someone
in the middle seat who's not strapped in
I don't sure they I can't okay so this
is comma two running on the pulse desire
branch and let's just make sure
so we'll go for a little drive around to
the highway
the guys were working also on the
autopilot in the in the city or now well
I can show you what it'll do so we don't
we don't block where it can engage or
not ah so we'll just uh let's get the
highway first but yeah so the first
thing you learn about self-driving cars
if they're actually extremely bored when
it works well it's super boring when it
doesn't work well it's exciting but you
know that's not good so as it gets
better these demos get more and more
boring
so the Corolla is a out-of-the-box it's
the best car we have but a torque modded
Civic is slightly better because the
Corolla has some issues with the rate
limiter
so let's just do it automatically in
change here
pulse desire stuffs good oh it used to
be so aggressive and they change
so yeah yeah the problem with these
demos and like we learned this quick
doing demos for the press is when it
works this partnership
oh wow yeah so I'm not an exciting part
again you know what I mean like I'm not
like doing anything you know yeah look
back at you don't do that watch a rut
guys there's a girl are complaining yeah
it's not just kind of probably a bat
there you go oh there you go
yeah we don't to make the DM too
aggressive because it's too aggressive
and just piss people off
we'll try closing my eyes we'll see if
it detects that watch the road guys
waiting for Tesla to update their yes
activation for that if ever
yeah so
we know really bad accidents yep that
could happen a few where drivers fall
asleep so it turns out that like 1 in 20
drivers has fallen asleep in the last 30
days while they're driving
suffer scary
yeah are you waiting for Tesla up to 30
M they'll never do it and the reason why
is they don't have it for LEDs that's
what I was thinking yeah I was thinking
that the cameras are insensitive
and that the display has enough to show
some my own driver but probably
no it does not we know this we know this
from experience
yeah no one's actually seen an image
produced from that campaign really yeah
that's what I want to get done today -
that's just let's go in here
automatically change we're gonna
integrate real soon with the blind spot
monitor late it's gotten so much better
yeah pulse desires sick post desire we
used to put it we used to constantly say
lane change they change they change
elite actually change and now we just
say they change once
all right we'll go for the demo or it
might actually mess up this when you're
on highways like this it just never
makes mistakes unless some driver does
something like really stupid
yeah it's smoother than our patent on
the upside is it's smooth the downside
is it
not as tight for things that do require
Titans
I really like that we disengage on gas
you're thinking it's a domestic visit
because it goes over the Torah yeah I
don't know sometimes there's model
failures see what does on this merge up
here
we're not great at merger our
longitudinal policy just isn't great
problem like if there's a car like right
there kind of cutting in and it doesn't
detect it as a lead it'll accelerate
into it
I'm doing nothing
[Music]
it used to be more aggressive on the
accelerator well so at first it wasn't
aggressive on the accelerator at all and
then we had people complain that it
wasn't aggressive in accelerated
aggressively so then we had people
complain about their fuel biology so we
reverted a lot of the accelerator
aggressiveness we're still kind of
aggressive and stop and go traffic but
like that like get on and get in front
of somebody it won't do
auto pilot to a more aggressive
accelerator phone plenty of an electric
car you can't be you think yeah
you don't feel it as much because it's a
lectric you know it's not about you
don't feel like I feel less compared to
this look at how chill this it's alright
like our slogans make driving chill we
really try to we really try I like
optimize minute oh you know it's just
driving is this
I just don't model three-four fortunate
models inherent you have probably met a
thousand on autopilot and the first time
driving a pilot and a couple of weeks
and it's it's a different experience
like autopilot feels like it's
aggressively keeping you in the center
of the road and like it's like a you've
got a machine and it's like you know um
you know maybe like you know I think
like BMW slogan like ultimate driving
machine I mean that's what like
autopilot feels like a little bit of
element yeah that's not great we got out
we gotta fix that it's not like terrible
like it doesn't split the difference
anymore use this what the difference
take you right to the milk just get over
here
give me second automatically change
maybe my miss car nice job Oh violet
yeah
everybody happy with that
at first is something that competes with
the auto family does really well it's
just it is so much more of a autopilot
really like you know test the talks all
the time about my full cell driver plus
I'll drive a full self-driving we don't
do that we embrace the fact that it's an
assistant alright so I'm gonna have to
take control here because we actually
don't want to get off that sixth Avenue
and not be in hillcrist
still when you got to do maneuvers like
this
it's still all you
I haven't tried the full self-driving
stuff like Tesla might be able can Tesla
do that if what I just did there
not that wall not that well
so we got lane changes around corners
automatic end you're never gonna get
nagged as long as you are paying
attention to the road Amen you watch me
both look away and close my eyes so I
called me both times so it is definitely
so this stuff's actually quite harder
than it looks you look at her like oh
this is a normal turn yeah it's really
easy to read but look at the bank of the
room right
just a heads up and it might mess up
there a lot of times when we give that
warning we should we should actually
really quantify that like what our
percent of false positives and true
positives is on that we don't want to
well there are people too much but at
the same time if there's like really any
chance that it's gonna mess up
also our torque limit is so much lower
than Tesla's it scares me to keep my
hands off the wheel sometime for auto
pilot because it might just target it's
never
that's all that's all enforced by the
Panda it's not even don't like none of
the Python is the safety code the safety
codes all in C it's got great you're
gonna test this around it and we limit
the ramp up of torque so it can never a
jerk to realign that's why I'm so
confident having my hands off like it's
not to say that it doesn't mess up but
what it does mess up it's a Sheila reach
out and turn not
they're going to go I had thought that
Oracle that's were provided in that car
they are but we do additional we don't
actually you can use the max torque of
the Corolla but we it takes about two
seconds to ramp up to photographer so we
we put additional safety restrictions in
front of Toyota
we don't put additional safety
restrictions in front of Honda because
the Honda torque is so crappy to begin
with that we're like there's no way you
know it's gonna be fine alright so now
we're adding a little bit of stop and go
let's just get over here
it's an assistant so we don't put this
engage on steering but unlike autopilot
we do disengage on gas
I can tell you're pretty familiar with
where it disengages or where the I've
driven yeah
so his turn exceeds what that torque the
Macan do especially I'm taking at 50
miles an hour
I think that's one thing that really
does well
the miles from its users driven
to take those heart turns we can do it
too it's a safety thing it's not a it's
not a model thing or model critics are
turned great the problem is well if you
allow high torques right if your policy
is to allow high torques when the model
says high torque is okay then well what
if the model says high torque is okay
and it's like not so in cities how well
do we work this is where I think we are
comfortably better than all on my
location I think auto pilots better at
hard turns
I think auto pilots way better emerging
we do almost nothing for merging but
when you're in scenarios like this where
it's kind of like subtle maneuvering
we've on that water where's all the
pilots like all there's a plane over
there oh let me move over there oh
there's a lady over there over there
I think there sounds more applause than
August
so like look at look at the maneuvering
through I mean these are straight
intersection so they're not that tricky
but look at how we've like moved a
little bit out there but not too much
right like really like where a human
would position themselves on the road
so this vehicle have radar returns yep
now and you integrate those when doing
fusion
but yeah I mean this is this is the
tricky stuff look at look at look at how
it just look at what moved like a little
bit there and it's so subtle I'm to like
put you in between where the parked cars
and where the oh man and this isn't even
be efficient
yeah we've been 31 32 miles-per-gallon
with the new longitudinal policy and
went down to like 28
okay cool wow thanks George thank you
very much
do one more